Guide to the Time Inc. Library and Archives Records 1923-2013, undated MS 3009-RG 20
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
Time Inc. Library and Archives Records
1923-2013, undated
MS 3009-RG 20
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
50.0 Linear feet (50 boxes)
The Time Inc. Library and Archives Records contain the Library Reference Collection which includes annual reports, press clippings, and Time covers.
Time, inc.
Provenance
Gift of Time Inc. in 2015.
Related Archival Materials Note
This finding aid relates to just one record group of the Time Inc. Records. For information about the other record groups and for overall information about the archives, please see the Guide to the Time Inc. Records (MS 3009). The Henry Luce Papers (MS 3014) were acquired with the Time Inc. Records. The collection of books acquired with the records are cataloged as the Time Inc. Reference Library.
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers.
Arrangement Note
The record group is currently organized in one series, with additional series expected as future accruals are received and processed.
Scope and Contents Note
The Time Inc. Library and Archives Records contains the Library Reference Collection comprising reference material assembled by the Library and Archives.
Accruals Note
Further additions to this finding aid are expected.
Annual reports; Clippings (information artifacts); Corporate libraries -- New York (State) -- New York; Corporation records; Corporations--History; Corporations--New York (State)--New York; Library resources; Organization files; Publishers and publishing--New York (State)--New York; Time, inc -- History
- Series I. Library Reference Collection, 1923-2013, undated; 50.0 Linear feet (50 boxes)
  Arrangement Note
  Organized into three subseries:
  Subseries I.A. Annual Reports
  Subseries I.B. Press Clippings
  Subseries I.C. Time Covers
  Scope and Contents Note
  The Library Reference Collection contains reference material assembled by the Time Inc. Library and Archives including a run of annual reports, printouts of press clippings emailed to staff by Time Inc.'s corporate communications, and a run of Time covers.
  - Subseries I.A. Annual Reports, 1923-2013; 8.0 Linear feet (8 boxes)
    Time Inc. includes annual reports for Time Inc. and later Time Warner Inc. after the merger. The library kept a run of annual reports in binders from 1923 to 1988 and another run of loose annual reports from 1924 to 2013. America Online, Inc. (AOL) includes reports sent to the library for use as reference at the time of the merger. Annual reports may include accompanying financial reports, fact books, or Year in Review. Years missing from Time Inc. are 2008 to 2009 and 2011 to 2012.
    Organized chronologically.
    - Time Inc.: 1922-1970 (Offsite-box 656)
    - Time Inc.: 1971-1988 (Offsite-box 657, Folder 1-10)
    - Time Inc.: 1924-1946 (Offsite-box 657, Folder 11-12)
    - Time Inc.: 1947-1967 (Offsite-box 658)
    - Time Inc.: 1968-1981 (Offsite-box 659)
    - Time Inc.: 1982-1991 (Offsite-box 660)
    - Time Inc.: 1991-1998 (Offsite-box 661)
    - Time Inc.: 1998-2004 (Offsite-box 662)
    - Time Inc.: 2004-2007 (Offsite-box 663, Folder 1-7)
    - Time Inc.: 2010 (Offsite-box 663, Folder 8)
    - Time Inc.: 2013 (Offsite-box 663, Folder 9)
    - America Online, Inc., 1992-2000 (Offsite-box 663, Folder 10-11)
  - Subseries I.B. Press Clippings, 2005-2013; 34.0 Linear feet (34 boxes)
    - October 2005 - December 2005 (Offsite-box 678)
    - December 2005 - February 2006, 2005-2006 (Offsite-box 679)
    - February 2006 - April 2006 (Offsite-box 680)
    - April 2006 - May 2006 (Offsite-box 681)
    - May 2006 - June 2006 (Offsite-box 682)
    - June 2006 - July 2006 (Offsite-box 683)
    - July 2006 - August 2006 (Offsite-box 684)
    - August 2006 - October 2006 (Offsite-box 685)
    - October 2006 - November 2006 (Offsite-box 686)
    - November 2006 - December 2006 (Offsite-box 687)
    - December 2006 - January 2007, 2006-2007 (Offsite-box 688)
    - January 2007 - February 2007 (Offsite-box 689)
    - February 2007 - April 2007 (Offsite-box 690)
    - April 2007 - May 2007 (Offsite-box 691)
    - May 2007 - June 2007 (Offsite-box 692)
    - June 2007 - July 2007 (Offsite-box 693)
    - July 2007 - September 2007 (Offsite-box 694)
    - September 2007 - October 2007 (Offsite-box 695)
    - October 2007 - November 2007 (Offsite-box 696)
    - November 2007 - January 2008, 2007-2008 (Offsite-box 697)
    - January 2008 - February 2008 (Offsite-box 698)
    - February 2008 - April 2008 (Offsite-box 699)
    - April 2008 - July 2008 (Offsite-box 700)
    - July 2008 - October 2008 (Offsite-box 701)
    - October 2008 - February 2009, 2008-2009 (Offsite-box 702)
    - February 2009 - July 2009 (Offsite-box 703)
    - July 2009 - December 2009 (Offsite-box 704)
    - December 2009 - May 2010, 2009-2010 (Offsite-box 705)
    - May 2010 - August 2010 (Offsite-box 706)
    - August 2010 - February 2011, 2010-2011 (Offsite-box 707)
    - February 2011 - July 2011 (Offsite-box 708)
    - July 2011 - October 2011 (Offsite-box 709)
    - October 2011 - May 2012, 2011-2012 (Offsite-box 710)
    - June 2012 - October 2013, 2012-2013 (Offsite-box 711)
  - Subseries I.C. Time Covers, 1923-2009; 8.0 Linear feet (8 boxes)
    Time Covers contains a run of only the covers removed from the rest of the magazine.
    - 1923-1929 (Offsite-box 667)
    - 1929-1942 (Offsite-box 668)
    - 1943-1958 (Offsite-box 669)
    - 1959-1974 (Offsite-box 670)
    - 1975-1986 (Offsite-box 671)
    - 1987-2000 (Offsite-box 672)
    - 2001-2007 (Offsite-box 673)
    - 2007-2009, 8.0 Linear feet (8 boxes) (Offsite-box 674)